你好  迪恩
Hi, Dean.
盖思
Garth.
马默杜克  真够疯狂的
Oh, Marmaduke, you're crazy!
对他的好感是慢热型的
He grows on you.
我都错过什么了
What'd I miss?
你说得对  确实是慢热型的
You're right. He has grown on me.
那是人家跟我说的最中听的一句话了
That's the nicest thing anyone's ever said to me.
我不做猎人了
I don't hunt anymore.
-你退出了  -是的
- You quit? - Yeah.
是什么让你就那么退出了
What could possibly make you stop just like that?
是因为女孩吗
Was there a girl?
是  艾米利亚
Yeah. Amelia.
-好吧  你呢  -我怎么了
- All right, what about you? - What about me?
我叫本尼
I'm Benny.
看得出来你们两个有很多话要说
I can see you two have a lot to talk about.
如今
密苏里州  科尔尼
亲爱的
Hey, hon.
来得正好
Just in time.
给我拿杯冷饮  行吗
Grab me a cold one, would ya?
怎么不叫莎拉・奥尔科特给你拿
Why don't you have Sara Alcott get it for you?!
什么
What?
天呐
Oh, my god!
玛丽  救救我
Mary, help!
玛丽  你在干什么
Mary, what are you doing?!
玛丽  玛丽  救救我  把...
Mary! Mary, help me! Get the --
玛丽
Aah! Mary!
玛丽  不要
Mary! No!
《凶鬼恶灵》  第八季  第六集
南方风情
喂喂
Heads up.
我在警用扫描仪上听到了一桩案子
I caught wind of a case on this police scanner.
听着像是我们的活儿
Sounds like our kind of thing.
我离开还不到十分钟
I wasn't even gone 10 minutes.
好吧  那怎么了
Okay. That matters why?
我不知道  迪恩
I don't know, Dean.
比如  从普兰提斯岛回来你就没跟我说过话
How about because you haven't said a word to me since Prentiss Island?
怎么着  你就指望我坐在副驾  不说话
And now, what? You want me to shut up and ride shotgun
当什么事都没发生过吗
and act like nothing happened?
你想谈本尼的事吗
You want to talk about Benny?
-行  那就说呗  -好啊
- Fine. Let's talk. - Okay.
不如说说他是个吸血鬼
How about he's a vampire?
多亏了他我才站在这儿
He's also the reason I'm topside
而不是在炼狱里做烤肉
and not roasting on a spit in purgatory.
还想听什么
Anything else?
别弄得像我不理解你
Don't pretend I don't get it.
我知道你在下面身不由己
I know you had to do what you had to down there.
我十分怀疑你理解炼狱的任何事
I highly doubt you get anything about purgatory.
但你已经出来了  本尼却还活着
But you're out now, and Benny's still breathing.
为什么
Why?
他是我的朋友  萨姆
He's my friend, Sam.
那我的朋友艾米呢  她又怎么了
And what about my friend, Amy? She was what?
你杀她的时候可毫不含糊
'cause you sure as hell didn't have a problem ganking her.
人总是会变的  不是吗
Well, I guess people change, don't they?
我们还把狼人凯特放走了
We let that werewolf Kate go, didn't we?
因为她不一样  她...
She was different. She --
你觉得本尼也不一样
You think Benny's different?
他是不是说他不直接吸人血什么的
Did he tell you he's not drinking live blood or something?
你居然相信他
And you believe him.
行  你说得对  人是会变
Okay. You know, you're right. People do change.
没错  我找了个吸血鬼兄弟
Yeah. I got a vampire buddy,
而你把电话关了一年
and you turn your phone off for a year.
别扯到我身上
Don't turn this on me.
听着  如果本尼犯错了
Look, Benny slips up
其他猎人干掉了他  那就这样了
and some other hunter turns his lights out, so be it.
但绝不会是你  对吧
But it's not gonna be you, right?
你去不去
You coming or not?
这家伙正在车底下捣鼓
So, guy's old lady comes home
他老婆回到家里
while he's working underneath his ride,
一脚油门踩到底  削掉了他半个脑袋
puts the pedal to the metal, and takes half his head off.
就这样吗
What, that's it?
简而言之就是这样
Yeah, in a nutshell.
她说她昏过去了  什么都不记得了
She says she blacked out, doesn't remember a damn thing.
听起来像是疯了
Well, sounds like insanity.
可能吧
Maybe.
你为什么觉得这是我们的事
So, how does that make this our kind of thing?
萨姆  因为凯文不见了  行吗
Because, Sam, Kevin's in the wind, okay?
你就像个逛窑子的太监  闷闷不乐
You're sulking around like a eunuch in a whorehouse,
我忍不住问自己
and I can't help but ask myself,
削脑袋什么时候不是我的事了
when is decapitation not my thing?
联调局
FBI?
是啊  我们恰好就在附近
Yeah, happened to be in the neighborhood.
先是来了个德州骑警  现在又是你们
First a Texas ranger, now you guys?
德州骑警
Texas ranger?
对啊  先生  就在那边
Yes, sir. Right over there.
逗我玩儿呢
Oh, you got to be kidding me.
好啊  查克・诺里斯
Hey, Chuck Norris.
萨姆  迪恩
Sam? Dean!
忘了他多爱抱人了
Forgot he was a hugger.
-过来抱抱  -好吧  行啦
- Come here! - All right. Okay.
我们在处理公务呢
We're still -- we're still working here.
你们都不知道我有多想你们
Uh, you guys have no idea how much I missed you.
让我们单独待会儿  好吗
Um, excuse us, would you?
是  我们就过来
Yeah, we'll be right back.
德州骑警  盖思  你搞笑呢
A Texas ranger, Garth? Seriously?
这可是密苏里
We're in Missouri.
怎么了
What?
拜托  我穿着西装就像丧葬承办人
Come on. I look like a funeral director in one of those.
先前我听人说你们重出江湖了
I heard some chatter you two were back in the batter's box,
我还不信  现在我信了
but I didn't believe it till now.
稍等
Oh, uh, one sec.
厄尔  有什么情况
Yo, Earl. What you got?
一个幽灵
A revenant.
好吧  你准备一口棺材和几根银钉
Okay, uh, you'll need a casket and some silver spikes.
还有  别被咬到了
Oh, and don't get bit.
不会害你变异  但会疼死你
No, it won't turn you, but it will hurt like hell.
都找到后
Okay, so, once you got all that,
把那东西钉在棺材里  埋结实了
nail that sucker in, bury him, and throw away the key.
知道了吗
Okay?
就这样  再见
All right. Hasta.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
我的工作啊  伙计
My job, hombre.
-你的工作  -是啊
- Your "Job"? - Yeah.
你什么时候干起咨询来了
And since when is giving advice your job?
等等  你就是那个新鲍比吗
Hold up. Are you the new Bobby?
给我闭嘴
You shut your mouth.
是啊
Yes.
你也闭嘴
You shut your mouth.
真的
What?!
鲍比没了  你们俩都失踪了
Bobby was gone. You two were M.I.A.
那段时间很古怪的
It was a weird time.
总得有人来接手
Somebody had to step in and take up the slack.
好了
All right.
我们还是继续工作
Let's just get back to work,
过后再来谈这个事情  好吗
and we'll talk about this later, all right?
盖思刚刚是在指挥我们吗
Did Garth just tell us what to do?
斯科特・卢
Uh, Scott Lew.
这两位先生是联调局的人
These gentlemen here are with the FBI.
卢先生的父母就是这件...
Mr. Lew's parents were the individuals involved in this...
不幸事件的当事人
unfortunate situation.
节哀顺变
Sorry for your loss.
有几个问题  卢先生
Just a few questions, Mr. Lew.
你父母会不会  感情出现了什么问题
Um, by any chance were your parents having... marital problems?
没有  至多就是些小磕绊
No. Uh, no more than anyone else.
你母亲的健康状况如何
What about your mother's health?
这会不会是癫痫  中风发作
Any chance this was a seizure, a stroke,
有什么说得通的解释吗
anything that might help explain this?
我想没有
I don't think so.
他们正在医院给她做检查
Um, they're checking her out at the, um, hospital right now.
有什么古怪的表现吗
What about stranger behavior?
古怪  譬如说
Stranger? How?
听见幻声  看到幻象...
Hearing voices, seeing things --
你母亲提过这样的事情吗
Your mother mention anything like that?
我父母结婚三十多年了
My parents were married for 30 years --
高中时就是恋人
High-school sweethearts.
不管你们怎么查
There's no good explanation for why this happened,
这事根本解释不通
no matter where you want to look.
好吧  谢谢你  斯科特
Okay, well, thank you, Scott.
保持联系
We'll be in touch.
没有电磁干扰
No EMF.
没有硫磺的痕迹
No traces of sulfur anywhere.
不出所料  白跑了
Like I thought -- bust.
别这么着急  萨姆
Hold on there, Sam.
还有许多需要考虑的因素
There's a lot of things to factor in here.
这事是昨晚发生的
Uh, it happened last night,
读不到电磁干扰很正常
so the readings could be cold by now.
说得对
Good point.
再说了  即使有硫磺
And, uh, even if there was any sulfur,
[巴尼・法夫是搞笑电视剧中的副警长]
巴尼・法夫和他的手下
Barney Fife and his crew
恐怕是把犯罪现场
probably contaminated the whole crime scene
以及所有证据都弄乱了
and any evidence that was here with it.
他还真不赖
Wow. He's on a roll.
可以这么说
That's one word for it.
伙计们  我好像有发现
Uh, guys, I think I found something.
那是口香糖还是灵质
Is that gum, or is that ectoplasm?
灵质一般是黑的吧
Ectoplasm is usually black, right?
绝对是灵质
Definitely ectoplasm.
会是什么呢  应该是鬼魂吧
So, what are we thinking -- uh, some kind of ghost, right?
麦克雷骑警
Uh, Ranger McCrae here.
要是哪只手机铃是锤子乐队的  我就砸了它
If one of those things rings Hammer, I'm throwing down.
太好了
Oh, great.
好的
Okay.
谢了医生
Thanks, doc.
我嘱咐过法医
Asked the coroner to drop me a line
尸检如果有什么不寻常就通知我
in case the autopsy turned up anything... unusual.
你们猜怎么着
And guess what.
死者胸口刻着一个词  "奥尔科特"
Our dead guy had the word "Alcott" carved into his chest.
用什么刻的
With what?
据法医猜测
Coroner's best guess?
是他老婆玛丽的指甲
His wife Mary's fingernails.
卢太太  能给我们讲讲发生了什么吗
Mrs. Lew, can you tell us what happened?
我当时在商店买杂货
I was at the store getting groceries,
等我再回过神来
and the next thing I know,
我儿子斯科特发现我在车道上
my son Scott finds me in the driveway.
切斯特已经...
And Chester was...
你对发生的事有任何印象吗
Do you remember anything at all about what happened?
切斯特的死
Um... Chester dying?
不太记得
Not really.
只有零星的记忆
Bits and pieces, I guess.
比如呢
Such as?
我记得他的尖叫
I remember his screams...
橡胶灼烧的味道
the smell of burnt rubber, and...
我记得我非常愤怒
I remember feeling so angry --
无法抑制的狂怒  我不能自控
just uncontrollable rage, like I wasn't myself.
一切结束之后
And after it was over,
那种愤怒
all that anger was --
就消失了
It was gone.
夫人  "奥尔科特"这个词你熟悉吗
Uh, ma'am, does the word "Alcott" mean anything to you?
她跟这件事有什么关系
What does she have to do with anything?
是女的
It's a she?
高中时我和我丈夫切斯特恋爱了好几年
My husband, Chester, and I were going steady in high school
感情本来很稳固  却突然大吵一架
for a few years already when we had a big fight.
因为什么
What about?
就是件蠢事
Something stupid, I'm sure.
当时临近毕业舞会
It was around prom,
他却抛弃我邀请了莎拉・奥尔科特
and so he took Sara Alcott as his date instead of me.
这位莎拉・奥尔科特是你的情敌喽
So, this Sara Alcott was a rival for your husband's affections?
莎拉和他只过了一夜
Sara had one night with him,
我和切斯特过了整整37年
whereas I was with Chester for 37 years.
当然  这是当然
Of course, right. Sure.
最后一个问题
Um, just one more question.
这位奥尔科特女士还在世吗
Is... Ms. Alcott still alive?
据我所知  是的
As far as I know, yes.
非常感谢  卢夫人
Thank you very much, Mrs. Lew.
我说这算怎么回事
Let me get this straight.
这可怜的家伙
This poor guy
三十多年前跟别的女孩去毕业舞会
goes to prom with some girl over 30 years ago,
就为这个而变了肉饼
and because of that, he is now a pancake?
如果是鬼魂
I mean, if this is a ghost,
也许是恶灵附体
maybe it's some sort of possession?
你说什么呢
What are you talking about?
你也听到了  奥尔科特还活着
You heard her. Alcott's alive.
必须跟她谈谈
Well, we're definitely gonna want to talk to her.
嗯  有道理
Yeah, sounds like a plan.
我们吃饭了吗
Did we eat yet?
谢谢
Thanks.
再上点儿
Keep'em coming.
迪恩  透露下内幕
So, Dean, give me the skinny.
你这一年去了哪
Where were you this past year?
关于我暑假都干了什么下次再说吧
Why don't we save what I did on my summer vacation for another time?
快说嘛
Aw, come on.
好吧
All right.
我在炼狱
I was in purgatory.
真正的炼狱吗
Like the purgatory purgatory?
不  是迈阿密的那座
No, the one in Miami.
兄弟  那太该死了
Man, that's balls.
"该死"不是这么用的
That's not how you say "balls."
那你是怎么出来的
So how'd you get out?
怎么到处挂着南方邦联的旗帜
What's up with all the, uh, hillbilly hankies?
这些人知道南北战争早结束了吧
These people know the Civil War's over, right?
南北战争在这里是敏感话题
That's a touchy subject around these parts.
密苏里州曾经是南北交界处
See, Missouri was a border state.
一半人支持南方邦联
So, half the men were confederate,
另一半支持北方联邦
the other half were the union.
你怎么知道这些
How do you know all this?
我上过大学
I went to college.
你上过大学
You went to college?
是
Yeah.
大学  然后是牙科学院
College, and on to dental school.
你还做过牙医
What, you -- you were a dentist?
对呀  就那么一阵子
Yeah, just for, like, a hot minute.
你以为我怎么开始猎魔的
Where'd you think I got my first case?
让我猜猜  牙仙
Let me guess -- tooth fairy.
对
Yeah.
杀那个畜生时我难受极了
Man, I felt terrible when I ganked that S.O.B.
你杀了那个牙仙
Uh, you killed the tooth fairy?
是啊  兄弟
Yeah, man.
不是我最自豪的事情  但是事实
I mean, not my proudest moment, but it happened.
真好吃
Man, this is good.
喂  亲爱的
Hey, hon.
正要去医院  在这儿买杯咖啡
Uh, just, uh, grabbing some joe on the way to the hospital,
去给老妈送东西
gonna bring mom her stuff.
该死
Oh, crap.
杰夫也在
Jeff's here.
别担心  我没事
Don't worry, I'll be fine.
好的
Okay.
爱你
Love you.
斯科特  你好...
Hey, Scott, how's --
你父母的事情我都听说了
Uh, look, I heard about what happened with your folks.
真的非常遗憾
I'm really sorry.
如果有任何
If there's -- there's anything --
我帮得上忙的地方
I mean, anything -- that I can do,
请尽管说
just -- just ask, man. Please.
那就把钱还我吧  杰夫
How about getting me my money back, Jeff?!
老妈先来一出《天生杀人狂》
So, first the mom goes "Natural Born Killer,"
儿子立刻跟上
and now the son?
难道是有俄狄浦斯情结的鬼魂
Well, what do we got -- a ghost with an Oedipus Complex?
即恋母情结
我也不懂那是什么意思
I don't know what that means.
瞧瞧这个
Check that out.
苏塞克斯
"Sussex."
又是人名吗
What is that, another name?
不知道
I don't know.
警察怎么说
Hey, what'd the cops say?
不是吧
Aw, come on.
没说什么
Not much.
斯科特坚称当时无法控制自己
Uh, Scott insisted he wasn't in control of himself.
他说只记得一阵狂怒
Says all he remembers is a red-hot rage.
这算怎么回事  家族诅咒吗
So, what is this, some -- some kind of family curse?
那是鲍比的帽子吗
Is that Bobby's hat?
对  当然是
Oh, yeah. Sure is.
几年前一起追捕法国狼人
We worked a rugaru case together a few years back.
他落在我车里的  我留着做个...
He left it in my car, so I kept it as a...
纪念
memento.
-你干什么  -帽子不是这么戴的
- What are you doing?! - That's not how you wear it.
先生们  监控录像可以看了
Gentlemen, surveillance is up,
但是画面有干扰
but something is all screwy with it.
一定是摄像机坏了
Must be the camera.
谢谢  副警长
Yeah, thank you, there, deputy.
注意到他的头了吗
You guys see the head?
从前见过这种情况吗
Ever seen anything like that before?
这样的吗  没见过
Like that? No way.
怎么办
So?
我想我们得找莎拉・奥尔科特谈谈
So, I'm thinking we need to talk to Sara Alcott.
我找到她了  她现在叫莎拉・布朗
I found her -- although these days, she goes by Sara Brown.
不如这样吧
How about this?
我去找她
I'll check her out,
你们查查苏塞克斯
and you two see what you can find out about Sussex.
好的
Word.
好极了
Awesome.
我知道你大老远跑来不是为了喝茶  探员
Now, I know you didn't come all this way for my sweet tea, agent.
其实  我是为切斯特・卢的事而来
No. Um, actually, I'm -- I'm here about Chester Lew.
原来如此
Oh, yes.
真让人难过
So sad.
是啊
It is.
你真的跟切斯特约过会吗
Is it true you and Chester... dated a ways back?
联调局问这种问题可真是奇怪啊  不是吗
Well, that is an odd question for the FBI, isn't it?
你不会相信我问过多少奇怪的问题
You wouldn't believe the awkward questions I've had to ask people.
好吧
Yeah.
是的  没错
Well yes. Yes.
我和老色鬼切斯特一起参加过毕业舞会
Me and that old tomcat, Chester, we went to prom together.
就是这样
That's about it.
仅此而已吗
And that's all?
我算不上是个好女孩
Well, I wasn't exactly a good girl,
如果你是想问这个
if that's what you mean.
打那之后
And after that,
我以为我会和切斯特轰轰烈烈地爱一场
I-I thought that Chester and I were gonna be hot and heavy.
但是有缘无分
But it just wasn't meant to be.
一星期后  他就跟玛丽就私奔了
And, uh, a week later, he eloped with Mary.
那之后你跟他们还说过话吗
Did you speak much to Mary or Chester again after that?
倒是见过面  野餐之类的
Well, I'd see them about, you know -- picnics and such.
不过  玛丽把他看得很紧
But...Mary kept Chester on a pretty short leash.
说实话  我是翻篇了  可她却没有
Honestly, I'd moved on, but it seems she never did.
你说这是为什么呢
And why do you think that is?
我想在她的心里
Well, I guess in her mind,
我永远提醒着她切斯特曾经的背叛
I was a reminder of Chester's betrayal.
如果没有别的事
So, if that's all...
是的  非常感谢你的帮助
Yes, uh, thank you very much for your help.
我很久没有让自己如此随性了
It's been a long time since I let myself go like that.
我完全理解
Yeah, I know what you mean.
你问我是不是失去了谁
You asked me if I lost someone.
没错
I did.
我的丈夫
My husband.
八个月前他在阿富汗牺牲了
He died in Afghanistan eight months ago.
这一定很...
That must have been, um...
我无法想象
I can't imagine.
对
Yeah.
我们本可以长相厮守
We were together forever.
至少我以为会那样
Or at least it seemed that way.
然后有一天  唐突然参军了
Then one day, Don just enlists.
都没问我的意见
Didn't ask me,
只说他想去做该做的事情
just said something about wanting to do the right thing.
然后他就远渡重洋  留我孤身一人
Next thing I know, he's off overseas and I'm all alone.
我只有他的信和电话
I got a couple letters, some phone calls,
再就是军队上门通报死讯
and then a knock at the door.
就这样
Just like that.
我所到之处
And everywhere I looked,
都是人们的议论和同情
all I could see was judgment and pity
一切一切都让我想起唐
and just this constant reminder of Don everywhere.
所以我搬到了这里
So I moved here...
但是我却越来越糟
...and became even more of a hot mess than I already was.
直到你撞了条狗
And you hit a dog.
松手  小子
Easy there, flyweight.
上次你乱喝酒
Last time you drank a beer,
人都粘在地板上了
I had to pick you up off the floor.
参见S07E18
你真是个白痴
You're such an idjit.
白痴是生气时用来骂人的话
Idjit's supposed to be used angrily.
懂吗  我不爱听
Okay? Not happy.
不会用就别说
If you're gonna butcher it, don't say it at all.
好吧
Whoa, then. Okay.
虽然不关我的事
N-none of my business,
但这是因为你跟萨姆的事吗
but...this have anything to do with you and...Sam?
你说得对  这不关你的事
No, you had it right. It's none of your business.
好吧
Okay.
我只是觉得
It just seems that you guys
你们之间的关系有点紧张
are a little tense around each other.
我们很好
We're fine.
可以继续工作了吗
Can we get back to work?
好的
Yeah.
好
Okay.
好吧
All right.
我就想告诉你
Just, uh -- just letting you know
我可以为你们做任何事
that I'm here for you, for anything.
我知道有时候  鲍比会...
I know sometimes Bobby, he would --
你不是鲍比
You're not Bobby!
懂吗
Okay?
你永远不会成为鲍比  所以别闹了
You're never gonna be Bobby, so stop!
鲍比是我们大家的朋友  不仅属于你和萨姆
Bobby belonged to all of us, Dean -- not just you and Sam.
我只是用他教我的东西
Now, I'm just taking what he showed me
想要造福他人  仅此而已
and trying do something with it. That's all!
那你看看能不能在他那本破书里
Why don't you see if you can find something
找到什么有用的
in that bourbon-drenched book of his
我们也好早日离开南部
so we can get the hell out of Dixie, all right?
好  我看着呢
Yeah. I'm on it.
苏塞克斯不是"谁"  而是"什么"
"Sussex" is not a who, it's a what.
是一家一年前才倒闭的公司
It's a business that went belly-up about a year ago.
看这里
Look at this.
那个被斯科特爆头的家伙
So, the guy that Scott brained?
是他以前的合伙人  把公司搞破产了
His old business partner -- ran the company into the ground.
斯科特和杰夫是有矛盾的
So, Scott had a beef with Jeff.
看来是这样
Looks like.
我开扬声器了
Hey, you're on speaker.
莎拉・奥尔科特没问题
Sara Alcott's clean,
她只不过是
if you look past the fact that
跟切斯特在舞会之夜有一夜情罢了
she and Chester knocked boots on prom night back in the day.
好吧  那么...
Okay, so...
玛丽对莎拉怀恨在心
Mary has a grudge against Sara,
而斯科特对杰夫怀恨在心
and Scott has a grudge against Jeff.
这些线索除了让我头疼
Besides the fact this is making my head hurt,
跟鬼魂能扯上什么关系
how does this add up to a ghost?
伙计们
Guys!
鲍比在这儿写了
Bobby has it right here.
绿色粘液代表厉鬼的存在
Green goo equals a spectre.
也就是鬼魂吧
Which equals ghost, right?
对  算是吧
Mm, yeah, kind of.
厉鬼是想复仇的鬼魂
A spectre is an avenging ghost.
它会上身
It, uh -- it possesses you
发现宿主心中感受到的背叛
and finds out whatever betrayals you're feeling
再强迫宿主去报仇
and forces you to act on them.
鲍比提没提如何猎捕这东西
Bobby say anything in there about how we hunt these things?
他最后一次遇见厉鬼
Uh, the last spectre he encountered
是有人刚刚亵渎了一座附近的坟墓
rose shortly after someone desecrated a nearby grave.
而这里...
Which...
三天前刚有个墓地遭人亵渎
Uh, there was a grave desecrated locally three days ago.
这里提到
It says here...
这下麻烦了
This could get awkward.
怎么了
What?
无名士兵墓地
The unknown soldier?
你开玩笑吧
You're kidding me, right?
玛丽・卢杀死她丈夫的前一天
Mary Lew steamrolled her husband
恰好这地方被人搞了破坏
the day after this place was vandalized.
你想呢
Do the math.
无名士兵不是都埋在阿林顿[国家公墓]吗
But I thought the unknown soldier was buried in Arlington.
没错  但这是南方邦联无名士兵的陵墓
Yep, but this is the confederate tomb of the unknown soldier.
是这样的
See, the idea was,
他们找了一个尸体无法辨认的无名士兵
they took a faceless, nameless soldier they couldn't identien,
埋葬于此  纪念所有丧生的士兵
and they buried him here to commemorate all the soldiers who died.
大学里学来的吗
Did you learn that in college?
不  是内战重演活动
Nope -- civil war re-enactments.
年年都有  每年一次
Once a year, every year.
别嫉妒我
Don't hate.
守卫怎么办
Okay, uh, what about the guard?
他就是摆个样子  傍晚就走了
Uh, he's ceremonial. Gone by dusk.
-那我们今晚动手吗  -对
- So, then we do this tonight? - Yeah.
在南方佬的地盘上烧掉他们士兵的骨头
Burn a confederate soldier's bones in a town full of rednecks?
真棒
Sure.
我没看出有人搞破坏的痕迹
Place doesn't look disturbed to me.
警局的报告怎么说来着
What's the police report say?
他们说只是几个小孩来这里捣蛋
Uh, they think it was just some kids messing around.
他们找到了几个啤酒罐还有涂鸦
They, uh -- they found some beer cans, some graffiti.
棺盖当时是开着的
Oh, and the casket was open when they got here,
他们给关回去了
but they closed that back up.
但里面的东西还是跑了出来
Yeah, but not before casper had a chance to make a run for it.
那如果他们不碰这些东西
So, what? If they never touched this,
事情就不会发生吗
none of this would be happening?
从鲍比的书上来看是这样
Yeah, according to Bobby.
好吧  我们开始干活
All right, well, let's get this party started.
萨姆  过来搭把手
Sammy, you want to give me a hand?
使劲
And go.
看看这些小宝贝
Whoa. Check out this hardware.
你们知道这些多值钱吗
Do you guys know how much this is worth?
是啊  打开了为什么不顺手捞一笔
Yeah, but why open it up if you're not gonna take anything?
不知道
I don't know.
或许警察出现把他们吓跑了
Maybe the cops showed up and they had to split fast.
你确定这对厉鬼也会有用吗
You sure this will work, even on a spectre?
它也是鬼魂  不是吗
It's a ghost, isn't it?
烧掉骨头  鬼魂就死了
You burn its bones, the ghost disappears.
等等
All right. All right. All right. All right.
我觉得我们该说点什么
Uh, I kind of feel like we should say something, all right?
你不觉得吗
Don't you? Just...A little...
好吧
Sure.
北方赢了
We won.
替我把这个写好  道格
Write that up for me, would you, Doug?
救命  拜托
Help! Please!
你没事吧
Hey. You okay?
我需要  哮喘  吸入器
Need my...asthma...inhaler.
在证物袋里  拜托
From evidence. Please.
你怎么不自己写报告呢  警长
Why don't you write your own reports, Sheriff?!
不
No!
好了  都好了  走吧
Right, we're set, let's go.
赌十块钱  道格副警长对上司有意见
10 bones says deputy Doug had an axe to grind with his boss.
你怎么知道
How can you be so sure?
怎么回事啊
Ah, what the hell?
也许我们烧错人了
Maybe we torched the wrong redneck.
也许没错
Or maybe not.
只是罪魁祸首已经不在墓里了
Maybe an object was removed from the grave,
厉鬼就附在某个物件上
something the spectre's attaching itself to.
就像鲍比的酒壶吗
Like Bobby's flask?
说不通啊  伙计们
Um, I don't know, guys.
我们都看到了  那些孩子什么都没拿
You saw what I saw. Those kids didn't take anything.
也许拿了呢
Or they did.
厉鬼就被带出来了
And this spectre hitched a ride with it.
拿到物件的人就会被附体
And whoever has the object gets possessed.
那么现在谁拿到了物件  更重要的是
Okay. So, who's got the object, and, more importantly,
那人跟谁有仇
who do they got a grudge against?
你得集中精神  副警长
All right. We need you to focus, Deputy.
你的话可以救命
Other lives depend on it.
告诉我  你射杀了警长之后发生了什么
Tell me what happened after you shot the Sheriff.
我倒在地上
I was on the ground.
可能是卡尔把我放倒的
I think Karl tackled me,
我问他发生了什么
and I asked him what happened.
然后呢
And?
他没有回答我
He didn't answer me.
拿起我的枪就走了
He just took my gun and walked away.
他说了要去哪吗
Did he say where he was going?
我想  我肯定也伤到他了
I guess... I must have hurt him, too.
他说他要去医院
He said he was going to the hospital.
你俩尽量去查那个无名战士
You two find out what you can about the unknown soldier.
我去医院
I got the hospital.
萨姆
Hey, uh, Sam.
你要是想找人聊天
If you ever need to talk,
请记住  我随时奉陪
I just want to let you know that I'm here.
谈什么都行  生活  迪恩和你
About anything -- you know, life, uh, Dean, you.
我没事  多谢
I'm okay. Thanks.
你和迪恩好像都各说各话
I mean, it just seems like you and Dean are talking
没人愿意听对方说
but nobody's listening to each other.
我有个表亲  他现在不在了
I had this cousin once -- well, he's gone now --
他叫弗兰克
but his name was Frank.
弗兰克和我曾经共建...
Frank and I used to build...
你走的时候记得锁门
Uh, just lock up when you leave.
我迟到了
I'm late.
等等  什么
Wait, what?
我只是觉得我俩最好别产生什么误会
I just think it's better if neither of us get the wrong idea here.
好啊
O-okay.
我昨晚说了很多话
And I know I said a lot of things last night,
我知道没办法叫你忘记
and I know I can't ask you to forget them.
但是  忘了吧
But just...do.
为什么
Why?
因为我不需要你的同情
Because I don't need your pity.
我不需要你也对我流露其他人的那种...
I don't need you looking at me the way they all --
就那种眼神
like that.
你觉得我是同情你吗
Wait, um you think this is pity?
艾米利亚  我很高兴你告诉我唐的事
Amelia, I'm glad you told me about Don.
这让我能理解你
It helps me understand.
理解我的生活有多糟吗  你以为我不知道
How messed up I am? You think I don't know that?
你用不着同情我  萨姆
You don't have to feel sorry for me, Sam.
我不是那个意思
I didn't mean it like that.
行了  我快迟到了  那么...
Yeah, well, like I said, I'm late. So...
喂  你来不来
Hey, you comin'?
你们知道称他为"无名"战士是有原因的吧
You do know there is a good reason he's called the unknown soldier, right?
对  我们想查查这么些年来
Right. Uh, we were just hoping maybe a theory or two
会不会有什么说法
had been a floated around over the years --
当地的传闻
Something local, maybe?
确实有
There is one.
裁判
Hey, Ump.
记得我吗  你判我盗二垒
You remember me? I stole second!
卡尔  你这是做什么
Karl? What the hell are you doing?
你为什么要...
Why are you doing --
为什么要用你的脑干做芥末酱吗
Why am I gonna make mustard from your brain stem?!
我不知道
I don't know.
为什么罚我出局  裁判
Why did you call me out, Ump?
对不起
I'm sorry.
求你了
Please.
看来是没子弹了
Looks like you're shooting blanks.
好痒啊
Hey, that tickled.
联邦军的柯林斯下士
Corporal Collins of the union
射杀了他加入了邦联的兄弟万斯
shot and killed his brother, Vance, who fought for the confederacy.
本地的小伙子
Local boys.
就是说两兄弟在内战时是敌对双方
Wait, so two brothers fought on opposite sides of the Civil War?
据说万斯死前起誓要找兄弟报仇
Legend has it that Vance swore vengeance on his brother with his dying breath.
多年后  无疑是因良心不安
Years later -- consumed by guilt, no doubt --
下士从他当年埋兄的
the Corporal dug his brother up
战场上把尸体挖了出来
where he'd buried him on the battlefield
带回了家
and brought him home.
你是说这个万斯就是无名战士
Are you suggesting this Vance guy is the unknown soldier?
有这种说法
That's one theory, anyway.
这是什么
What's that?
卡尔  听着
Karl, listen,
我知道是厉鬼让你发火
I know the spectre's turning the temperature up in there.
告诉我通灵物件是什么
So just tell me what the object is,
我们把这个捣蛋鬼送回去
and we'll send this joker home.
我可不这样想
I don't think so.
托你的福  事情还没完呢
There's unfinished business, thanks to you.
厉鬼喜欢你
Oh, the spectre likes you.
是吗
Oh, yeah?
不如你让他出来
Why don't you tell him to come on out here?
我们做对儿情侣镯
We'll make promise bracelets.
大多数士兵都是穷苦农民
Most of the soldiers were poor farmers,
家人会用绳子穿一分钱给他们
so the families would give them a penny on a string.
1859年  印第安人头像硬币
算是护身符  而且万一迷路了
It was for good luck, and in case they ever got lost,
还有一分钱买吃的喝的
they always had a penny for food or drink.
一分钱
A penny.
拿去  试试吧
Here. Have a taste.
是我  留言吧
It's me. Do what you gotta.
迪恩
Dean, hey.
墓地的地上有根绳子
There was a string on the floor of the tomb.
原本穿着一枚硬币
It used to hold an old penny.
那就是通灵物件
That's the object.
我们这就过来
We're coming right now.
迪恩  怎么回事
Dean? What the hell, man?
我们去了医院  你不接电话
We went to the hospital. You're not answering your phone.
我在炼狱的时候你本该去找我
You should have looked for me when I was in purgatory.
三天前
清醒点  迪恩
Come on, Dean.
我知道这不是你
I know it's not you in there pulling the strings.
闭嘴
Shut up!
别动
Don't!
你根本就不想要这种生活
You never even wanted this life.
你总是怪我又拉你下水
Always blamed me for pulling you back into it.
-不是这样  -真的吗
- That's not true. - Really?
自从你跟我上了路
'cause everything you've ever done
你做的每件事都是欺骗我
since you climbed into my ride has been to deceive me.
你想要我说什么
What do you want me to say?
说我有错吗
That I've made mistakes?
我是有错  迪恩
I've made mistakes, Dean.
他已经不是迪恩了  萨姆
That's not Dean, Sam.
闭嘴
Shut up!
有错
Mistakes?
那我们就来细数一下小萨姆的伟大功绩
Well, let's go through some of Sammy's greatest hits.
饮恶魔血
Drinking demon blood, check.
与露比合谋
Being in cahoots with Ruby.
瞒着我你没了灵魂的事
Not telling me that you lost your soul.
还跟随萨穆埃尔一整年
Or how about running around with Samuel for a whole year,
就让我以为你死了
letting me think that you were dead
而你却在为所欲为
while you're doing all kinds of crazy.
这些不叫有错  萨姆
Those aren't mistakes, Sam.
而是选择
Those are choices!
行  你说得对
All right. You said it.
我们俩都有点轻率了
We've both played a little fast and loose.
对  我也许会撒谎  但绝不曾背叛你
Yeah, I might have lied, but I never once betrayed you.
绝不曾不管你的死活
I never once left you to die.
你为了什么  一个姑娘
And for what, a girl?
你为了个姑娘扔下我不管
You left me to die for a girl?!
盖思  不要
Garth, don't.
别担心  他不会杀了我的
No, he won't kill me.
他怨念的不是我
His beef isn't with me.
你不会朝我开枪的对吗  迪恩
You're not gonna shoot me, are you, Dean?
走开
Move.
别这样  迪恩
Come on, Dean.
你不会想杀了你弟弟的
You do not want to kill your brother.
你这辈子都在保护他
You -- you've been protecting him your whole life.
现在也一样
Don't stop now.
他任由我在炼狱里自生自灭
He left me to rot in purgatory!
好吧  也许是的  我不清楚
All right. All right. Maybe he did. I don't know.
我不知道内情  但他肯定自有原因
I wasn't there. But I'm sure he had his reasons.
就像你留着本尼也自有原因
Just like you had your reasons for Benny.
谁
Who?
过去的一年里
Benny has been more of a brother to me
本尼对我的兄弟义气你永远都比不上
this past year than you've ever been!
没错
That's right.
小卡让我失望
Cass let me down.
你让我失望
You let me down.
唯一从没让我失望的就是本尼
The only person that hasn't let me down is Benny.
我知道你很生气
I know you're angry.
不过老兄  你得与这东西抗争
But, man, you got to fight this thing.
别这么做
Do not do this!
放下恩怨吧
Just let it go.
拜托了  迪恩
Come on, Dean.
再见了  萨姆
Goodbye, Sam.
天呐
Ow! God!
盖思  别捡
Garth, don't!
没事
It's cool.
没关系  我没事
It's all good. I'm cool.
我费了九牛二虎之力才熔了那枚硬币
It took me forever to melt that penny,
不过总算搞定了
but it's finally gone.
你怎么不像其他人一样被硬币控制了呢
How come that penny didn't jack you like everyone else?
我理解它怎么不能影响拿走它的孩子
I mean, I can understand why it didn't affect the kid who took it.
他年轻  单纯
He's young and innocent.
可是  无论谁这一生中总有
But, uh, everyone at some point in their life
觉得自己被耍了的时候
feels like they've been screwed.
我没有  兄弟
Not me, man.
我靠练瑜伽把那些都放下了
I let all that stuff go with the help of my yogi,
还有世嘉创世游戏
my Sega Genesis.
你也该这样
And you should, too.
历史是无从改变的  朋友
You can't change the past, amigo.
对了  我有话想跟你说
Now, there's something I want to say to you.
别再那么白痴了
Stop being a idjit!
鲍比死了  你和萨姆是彼此的唯一
With Bobby dead, you and Sam are all each other has.
这没那么糟  兄弟
And that's not so bad, man.
好了  你知道该怎么做了吗
Now, you know what's coming next, right?
来吧
Come on.
快点
好吧
Yeah, okay.
好好干  盖思
Keep on truckin', Garth.
谢了
Thanks.
该走了
Oh, got to go.
喂  拉马尔  什么情况
Yo, Lamar. What do we got?
雪怪温迪戈
Wendigo?
你有信号枪吗
You got a flare gun?
没有
No?
那喷火器呢
What about a flame thrower?
那最好备几双跑鞋了  伙计
Then you'd better get some sneakers, buddy,
因为你得跑路了
'cause you're gonna have to run.
好
All right.
该死
Balls!
萨姆  我做不到
Sam, I can't.
我不是同情你  好吗
I don't pity you. Okay?
不是
I don't.
你和我  我们有很多毛病
You and I -- we're a lot of things,
但我们不需要同情
but we're not to be pitied.
几个月前我失去了哥哥  迪恩
Look, I lost my brother, Dean, a few months ago.
我的世界好像崩塌了
It felt like my world imploded
那一切向我袭来  于是
and came raining down on me, and...
我逃了
I ran.
和你一样
Just like you.
你这番话是想鼓励我吗
Is that supposed to be a pep talk?
是的  大概吧
Yeah, uh, sort of.
因为
Because...
我开始同情你了
see, now I pity you.
其实  我倒不是这个意思
Oh, look, I mean, that wasn't really my point.
可我就是这个感觉  所以...
Yeah, well, bell's rung on that one, so...
那么
So, uh...
那么我们现在干什么
So what now?
我不知道
I don't know.
你想好好聊聊吗
You want to talk about it?
昨晚的事
Last night?
不是  是迪恩  你个变态
No. Dean, you pervert.
好  好的  我很乐意
Yeah. Yeah, I'd like that.
你想说说唐吗
Do you want to talk about Don?
我乐意听你说
Hey, I'd like that, too.
小萨姆
Sammy!
我就说一声  那姑娘  她叫艾米利亚
For the record, the girl -- her name's Amelia.
艾米利亚・理查森
Amelia Richardson.
我们在德克萨斯州的科米特有个住处
She and I had a place together in Kermit, Texas.
老实说我都不太记得我说什么了
Look, man, I don't even remember what I said,
不过
but, uh --
不过什么
But what?
不过那不是真心话吗  别骗人了
But you didn't mean it? Oh, please.
我们都清楚你不用那枚硬币就能说出那番话
You and I both know you didn't need that penny to say those things.
别这样  萨姆
Come on, Sam.
说什么就认了吧  迪恩
Own up to your crap, Dean.
你一回来我就说了自己都去过哪
I told you from the jump where I was coming from,
我为什么没去找你
why I didn't look for you.
你呢
But you?
你有秘密
You had secrets.
你有本尼
You had Benny.
你一回来就高高在上
And you got on your high and mighty,
对我咄咄逼人
and you've been kicking me ever since you got back.
这都过去了
But that's over.
都忘了吧  否则我就走人
So move on, or I will.
好
Okay.
我知道了
I hear you.
很好
Good.
我跟你说  还有
You know what? Hear this, too.
我或许就会是
I just might be that hunter
那个碰到本尼还结果了他的猎魔人
that runs into Benny one day and ices him.
我想这事是车到山前必有路  对吗
I guess we'll cross that bridge when we come to it, won't we?
对
Yeah.
你总是这句话
Yeah. You keep saying that.